nfm.com 2017-06-09

# Your privacy

Your privacy and the security of your personal information are very important to us. We want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our Website. We are dedicated to protecting the privacy of those who visit our Website. This Privacy Policy governs the NFM.com website operated by Nebraska Furniture Mart, Inc. (our “Website”) and explains how we collect your personal information on our Website, how we protect such information, and the choices you have concerning the use of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Except as we disclose in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, share, license, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website or any of our features, tools or resources that we provide on our Website, including without limitation, any fee based products or offerings (collectively, our “Online Products”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Please remember that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by our Website. We are not responsible for the privacy of any information you reveal or post in any public forum (e.g., message board or chat room), or for the privacy practices of websites that are operated or owned by third parties.**

**WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT ME IS COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE?**

We collect two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information.

**_Personally Identifiable Information._**

Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”). Such Personally Identifiable Information may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, age (primarily for eligibility purposes), and billing and credit card information. We may request Personally Identifiable Information from you when you register on our Website, purchase products online or in connection with other services we may make available on our Website from time to time. In all of these cases, we will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Unless you give us permission to do so, we will not sell, share, license, trade or rent your Personally Identifiable Information other than as specified in this Privacy Policy. You do not have to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information to visit our Website. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, you may not be able to visit all sections of our Website or purchase our products. In addition, we may not be able to provide you with some of the other services we offer that are dependent upon the collection of such information. 

**_Non-Personally Identifiable Information._**

When you visit our Website we may collect information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Website (“Non-Personally Identifiable Information”). Non-Personally Identifiable Information is used to help us understand who uses our Website and to improve and market our Website in general and our products in particular.

**WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE (INCLUDING THROUGH THE USE OF COOKIES)?**

We may collect information (including information that is Personally Identifiable Information) from you in different manners and at different places and times on our Website. We also may collect information from you in connection with, or through, other information or services we may make available on our Website from time to time. The following is a description of the areas and/or manners in which we primarily collect information about you.

**_Cookies._**

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information passively using “cookies.” “Cookies” are small text files that are placed on your computer in order to identify your Web browser and the activities of your computer on our Website and other websites. Cookies are used to personalize your experience on our Website (such as dynamically generating content on web pages specifically designed for you), and to allow us to statistically monitor how you are using our Website to help us improve our online offerings. We also may use cookies to target certain advertisements to your browser which may be of interest to you or to determine the popularity of certain content. While you are not required to accept our cookies to access our Website, if you reject cookies, certain products, offerings, features, or resources of our Website may not work properly and you may experience some loss of convenience.

**_Online Products._**

We collect information, some of which may be Personally Identifiable Information, that you voluntarily provide to us when you choose to purchase our products online. We also collect information that you provide voluntarily through responses to special offerings such as surveys, questionnaires, self-assessment quizzes, contests and the like. Some of these special offerings may ask you for additional information. We collect this information in order to offer you products or services that we think may be of interest to you.

**_Submission of Material._**

Any information, including but not limited to remarks, applications, comments, suggestions, ideas, graphics or other submissions (“User Content”) is the intellectual property of the specific users of the Web Site who post such User Content and their licensors, if any. NFM does not claim any ownership rights in such User Content. By posting User Content via the Web Site, however, you hereby grant to NFM a limited, transferable, nonexclusive, worldwide, perpetual, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, modify, edit, adapt, publish, translate, display, distribute, sell, sub license and create derivative works and compilations incorporating such User Content. 

**_Reviews and Comments._**

In addition to the rights applicable to any material you submit or post to the Website and/or provide Nebraska Furniture Mart, including without limitation, ideas, know-how, techniques, questions, reviews, comments, and suggestions (collectively, "Submissions"), when you post comments or reviews to the Website, you also grant Nebraska Furniture Mart the right to use the name that you submit with any review, comment, or other User Content, if any, in connection with such review, comment, or other content. You acknowledge and agree that any Submissions or User Content are provided on an uncompensated basis, without any promise or expectation or remuneration or other compensation payable by Nebraska Furniture Mart or its affiliates. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the reviews, comments and other User Content that you post on this Website and that use of your reviews, comments, or other User Content by Nebraska Furniture Mart will not infringe upon or violate the rights of any third party. You shall not use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself or otherwise mislead Nebraska Furniture Mart or third parties as to the origin of any Submissions or User Content. Nebraska Furniture Mart may, but shall not be obligated to, remove or edit any Submissions (including comments or reviews) for any reason. 

**Nebraska Furniture Mart Mobile Alerts Terms & Conditions**

To Join Mart Deals & Mobile Alerts: Text NFM (your email address) to 80565. You will receive up to 8 messages per month. Message and data rates may apply. 

Compatible carriers include: AT&T, T-Mobile, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Alltel, U.S. Cellular, and Cellular One.

To discontinue receiving SMS messages from NFM Mobile Alerts text **NSTOP** to 80565.

For additional help, text NHELP to 80565 or call 

By submitting enrollment, you agree to receive mobile contacts from Nebraska Furniture Mart including up to 8 SMS messages per month. You also affirm that you are 18 years of age or older, are authorized to agree to receive mobile contacts on the enrolled phone number and are responsible for an mobile message or data charges incurred. By confirming opt-in, persons 15 to 17 years of age are confirming parental consent to enroll their number into Mobile Alerts except where restricted by state law.

**DOES OUR WEBSITE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE?**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Our Website is not designed for or directed to children under the age of 13. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. We urge all parents or guardians to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online. If a child has provided our website with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian call or  contact us and we will delete the information about the child from our files.

**WHAT DOES OUR WEBSITE DO WITH THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?**

In general, we use the information collected on our Website to help us understand who uses our Website and how it is used, to personalize your online experience, to assist you in using our products, and to improve our Website. If you become a registered user of our Website, we may use your information to send you a welcoming email that may confirm your username and password. If you "opt-in" we may send you electronic newsletters, contact you about our products, services, information and news that may be of interest to you. If you no longer desire to receive these communications, we will provide you with the option to change your preferences. We may also use the information collected to send you important service announcements and updates regarding our Website or products.

**WHEN DOES OUR WEBSITE DISCLOSE INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES?**

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any information we gather from you on our Website.

We may disclose information (including Personally Identifiable Information) about you to our Affiliates. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Affiliates” means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with Nebraska Furniture Mart, Inc., whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that we provide to our Affiliates will be treated by those Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

We may also disclose your information (including Personally Identifiable Information)if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with an applicable statute, regulation, rule or law, a subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process. We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information in special circumstances when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our  Terms of Use to protect the safety and/or security of our users, our Website or the general public.

We may provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of our Website. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit our Website, the demographic breakdown of our registered user of our Website, or the activities that visitors to our Website engage in while on our Website. The third parties to which we may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising services (including website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties. 

**DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY WHEN I LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES?**

Our Website contains links to other websites not owned or operated by Nebraska Furniture Mart, Inc. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. We encourage you to be aware when our Website links to other websites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Website.

**IS THE INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE SECURE?**

We want your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to remain as secure as possible. We strive to provide secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers through industry-standard techniques. We endeavor to secure the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers which we believe are located in controlled, secure environments, protected from unauthorized access, use, or alteration. Only employees and authorized agents, vendors and suppliers who need access to your information to perform a specific task or function are granted access to such information. In addition, all Nebraska Furniture Mart, Inc. employees must abide by this Privacy Policy and are kept up-to-date on security practices. Any employee who violates this Privacy Policy is subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination. We also require that our authorized agents, vendors and suppliers (i) protect the privacy of your Personally Identifiable Information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (ii) not use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us with products or services for which we contracted.

Notwithstanding the above commitments to protect your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) from loss, misuse or alteration by third parties, you should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart our security systems. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE REGARDING THE COLLECTION, DISCLOSURE AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information for the purposes described above or as otherwise disclosed at the time we request such information from you. You must “opt-in” and give us permission to use your Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose. For example, we have an “opt-in” mechanism so that those who become registered users or subscribe to our Website must give us permission to send them marketing materials and our electronic newsletter. 

**CAN I UPDATE OR CORRECT MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**

You can always contact us in order to (1) update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (3) delete the Personally Identifiable Information maintained about you on our systems, by contacting  customer care. Such updates, corrections, changes and deletions will not have an effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third-parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our system. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personally Identifiable Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. We promise that promptly after receiving your request, all Personally Identifiable Information stored in databases we actively use and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable.

**HOW WILL I KNOW IF THERE ARE ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**

Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our Website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner significantly different from that stated in this Privacy Policy, or otherwise disclosed to you, at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Personally Identifiable Information in the new manner. We may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your Personally Identifiable Information. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use our website.

**WHO DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS?**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of our posted Privacy Policy, please contact us, who serves as our Privacy Coordinator, via site feedback.

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.
